question_data = [
    
{ "question": "Titanfall is a game made by Respawn.","answer": "True"}, 
   
{"question": "Titanfall is a game where you take care of a city as well as protect it from outsiders.", "answer": "False"},  
  
{ "question": "There are three games in the titanfall series.", "answer": "True"},  

{"question": "The second game was the only game with a story mode", "answer": "True"},

{"question": "In the story mode of the game the main character is named Viper", "answer": "False"}, 

{"question": "As you play along in the story you switch between characters", "answer": "False"},

{"question": "One of the other characters in the story is named BT-7274", "answer": "True"},  

{"question": "In the multiplayer gamemode of the two first game the max level was 100", "answer": "False"},

{"question": "The third game in the titanfall series changed from the usual gamemodes to becoming a battle royal game", "answer": "True"},

{"question": "During the last mission of the second game BT-7274 saves you from certain death and sacrifices himself", "answer": "True"}

]